Guide to the Robert Roth papers, 1973-1990
Roth, Robert papers, 1973-1990
- Series III. International Files
  - Volumes
    - A Homossexualidade no Mundo (Box 10)
    - Spartacus Guide (several years) (Box 10)
    - Now the Volcano (Box 10)
    - Sodoma (Box 10)
    - The Unmentionable Vice, by Michael Goodich (Box 10)
    - Game-Texts - A Guatemalan Journal (Box 10)
    - CelebrAsian (Box 10)
- Series IV. Legal Files
  - Frank Balash - Coop Sale (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Balakian Corporation (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Chuck Bailey (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Herman Badillo (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Richard Bearse (Box 11, Folder 7-9)
  - Anthony Barbieri (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Helene Baldizzone (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Allen Baum (Box 11, Folder 12-16)
  - Bell v. AdView (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
  - Gaysweek Reorganization (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Gaysweek - Legal (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Gaysweek - Advance Offset (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
  - Mercedes Beato (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Danny Beauchamp (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Jay Baez (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
  - Phillip Basnight (Box 11, Folder 27-31)
  - Don Barrington (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Marge Barton (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Michael Barrett (Box 11, Folder 34-35)
  - Raymond Barci (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Legal (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Richard Bearse (Box 11, Folder 38-39)
  - Allen Baum (Box 11, Folder 40-42)
  - Chin - Hudson View Properties - Weiss (Box 11, Folder 43-51)
  - 420 East 80th Company v. Chin (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Political - Roommates (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Evangelista Associates v. Bland (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chin, Harlow (Box 12, Folder 4-15)
  - 420 East 80th Company v. Chin, Harlow (Box 12, Folder 16-29)
- Series V. AIDS File
  - Alternate Therapies (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - AIDS Treatment News (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Healing AIDS (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Coalition Newsline (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - PWA Coalition Newsline (Box 13, Folder 7-13)
  - US Magazine article, 31 AUG 1982, "Mysterious Cancer that's Killing Gay Men" (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Treatment News back issues (Box 13, Folder 15-17)
  - Review of the Public Health Service's Response to AIDS (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Federal Response to AIDS: Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Government Operations, House of Representatives (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - AIDS Testing (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - AIDS Forum (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Strategies for Survival - A Gay Men's Health Manual for the Age of AIDS (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Surviving and Thriving with AIDS (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - First in the Fight Against AIDS, GMHC (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous AIDS Booklets, Publications, and Printed Information (Box 13, Folder 25-35)
- Series VI. Printed Miscellany
  - Miscellaneous brochures, newsletters, mailings, correspondence, pictorial material, and other kinds of printed miscellany (Box 14, Folder 1-40)
Separated Material
Separated from the Robert Roth Collection (#7325, box 1, folders 10 and 11) to be catalogued separately:
Paz Y Liberacion
No. 7 (Mar. 1985)
No. 16 (Mar.-May 1989)
No. 17 (June-July 1989)
No. 19 (Nov.-Dec. 1989)
Spanish edition:
No. 8 (Oct.-Dec. 1988)
Asian edition:
No. 1 (Jan.-Mar. 1989)
Africa/Middle East edition:
No. 1 (July-Dec. 1989)
Other separated materials (formerly in Box 10):
Japanese volumes
Selected Index To The Robert Roth Periodicals And Publications
Advocate Box 3, folder 7
Afuera Box 9, folder 36
Aghois Box 9, folders 26-28
AIDS Forum Box 13, folder 21
AIDS Treatment News Box 13, folder 4 Box 13, folders 15-17
All Lavender - International Gay Guide Box 5, folder 7
Amsterdam Gay Press Box 9, folder 14
Asians and Friends - New York Box 5, folder 2
Bizar 2 - International S/M Quarterly Box 5, folder 4
Body Politic - Gay Liberation Journal Box 6, folder 33
Broad Street Journal Box 2, folder 36
CelebrAsian Box 10
Center Happenings Box 2, folder 44
Center Sports Box 2, folder 45
Center Stage Box 2, folder 43
Center Voice Box 2, folder 40
Chorus Lines Box 2, folder 90
COC International Newsletter Box 9, folder 15
Desert Patrol Box 5, folder 18
DNF 48 Box 9, folder 22-23
El Otro Box 7, folder 21
Ellos Box 7, folder 20
Entender Box 7, folder 9
Footman Box 2, folder 91
Fuori! Box 8, folders 21-29 Box 9, folders 2-6
Gai Pied Lesbia Guide Box 10
Gaia's Guide Box 15, folder 9 Box 10
Game-Texts - A Guatemalan Journal Box 10
Gay Insurgent Box 3, folder 25
Gaysweek Box 2, folder 1
Greater Gotham Business Council Newsletter Box 4, folder 5-10
Guide Gai du Québec Box 10
Handyman Box 2, folder 92
Hombres Box 7, folder 20
Homosexuality in Canada Box 5, folder 6
Homossexualidade no Mundo Box 10
International Gay Association News Box 4, folder 28-38
Italia Gay Box 10
Jamaica Gaily News Box 8, folders 13-15
Jornal do Gay Box 7, folder 9
Lambda Box 8, folders 3-7
Lambda - Barcelona Box 9, folders 29-32
Lambda Update Box 2, folder 63
Lampião Box 7, folders 6-8
Latitudes - Journal of the International Lesbian and Gay Assocation Box 4, folder 26
Les Homosexuels s'Organisent Box 10
New York City News Box 5, folder 42
New Zealand Gay News Box 9, folders 16-18
Now the Volcano Box 10
Nuestro Cuerpo Box 8, folder 38
Nuevo Ambiente Box 8, folder 39
OG - Oriental Guys Box 5, folder 3
OMPO Box 8, folders 8-12
Out! Box 9, folders 19-20
Out/Look Box 2, folder 22
Outcome - Man-Age Press Box 2, folder 39
Outcry Box 2, folder 87
Pafuera! Box 9, folders 24-25
Pan Box 9, folders 11-12
Panorama Box 8, folder 41
Paz y Liberacion Box 1, folder 10 Separated Material
Pleiguei - O Jornal do Homo Box 7, folder 5
Politica Sexual Box 8, folder 40
Pride Guide Box 2, folder 26
Rainmaker Box 2, folder 94
Reporter - Den Oberoende Gaytidningen I Norden Box 5, folder 8
Revolt Box 5, folder 56 Box 10
Revolt - Mot Sexuella Fördomar Box 5, folder 10
RFA Box 2, folder 95
Rites Box 5, folder 9
Roth Newsletter Box 1, folder 21 Box 3, folders 49-51
Sek Box 9, folder 9-10
Sexual Law Reporter Box 1, folders 41-44
Sierra Domino Newsletter Box 4, folder 39
Sodoma Box 10
Somos Box 7, folders 2-3
Spartacus Box 9, folder 13
Spartacus Guide Box 5, folder 26 Box 6, folders 50-58 Box 10
Swiss Gay Box 9, folder 33
Undercoverman Box 2, folder 96
Viking Box 5, folder 5
Volunteer Box 2, folders 70-71